#### Contact

v\_allenrn@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/vicki-d-allen-39165161 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
BLS

ACLS

**Acute Care** 

# Vicki D. Allen

RN - Kaiser HH & Palliative Care

Novato, California

### Summary

I am a caring RN with main focus of Home Health and Palliative Care with occasional Hospice & Progressive Care Nursing. I work for Kaiser Permanente in Marin/Sonoma Co in CA . I have learned numerous EMRs, worked in many different settings across the U.S. Gaining a wealth of knowledge of how different HH&H agencies work. Love my patients and being able to teach them and assist them to live the best life possible. I do not consider nursing a job. For me it is a calling. My family consists of my mom, 2 grown sons and a daughter-in-law, all of whom I am very proud of. God has richly blessed me with the important things in life.

## Experience

doTERRA International LLC

https://www.mydoterra.com/healingmetoo/#/ January 2017 - Present (3 years 7 months)

Novato, California

On a Journey to health using essential oils. Contact me if you are interested in getting healthy!

Kaiser Permanente

Home Health Nurse

December 2016 - Present (3 years 8 months)

San Rafael, California

**AMN** Healthcare

RN Home Health & Hospice Travel Nurse

July 2015 - December 2016 (1 year 6 months)

Novato, CA

Kaiser Permanente Home Health, Novato, CA. 02/08/16-present. Sentara Rockingham Hospice, Harrisonburg, VA (Cerner 5) 07/15-01/16

LHC Group RN Hospice Nurse March 2015 - July 2015 (5 months)

**AMN Healthcare** 

RN Home Health & Hospice

December 2013 - March 2015 (1 year 4 months)

Travel RN for American Mobile Health Care. Assignments - Sutter Care @ Home (ERM Home Care Home Base) Novato, CA 12/13-6/14. Sentara Hospice (EMR Cerner) Harrisonburg & Chesapeake VA 6/14-12/13. Riverside Walter Reed Hospice (ERM McKesson) Gloucester, Va. 1/15-3/15.

Mission Health

**RN Supervisor** 

July 2011 - December 2013 (2 years 6 months)

Nursing Unit Supervisor of Med/Pulmonary Progressive Care Unit

AMN Healthcare

**RN Home Health** 

October 2008 - June 2011 (2 years 9 months)

Travel nurse providing care in patient's homes including Cardiac and Pulmonary disease management, wound care, diabetes education, IV infusions. Assignments included agencies: Sagebrush Home and Family Services in Bakersfield, CA; Marshall Homecare, Placerville, CA; Denton State School, Denton, TX; Sentara Home Health, Charlottesville, VA; Amedisys Home Care, Lexington, SC; and Professional Healthcare at Home, Pleasant Hill, CA.

Amedisys Home Health & Hospice

RN Home Health

November 2005 - April 2008 (2 years 6 months)

Managed patient home care from admission to discharge including Cardiac and pulmonary disease management; woundcare; IV infusions; diabetes education and management.

#### Education

Asheville-Buncombe Technical Community College Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1992 - 1994)

The University of Texas at Arlington

Courses, Bachelor of Nursing · (2011 - 2012)